"A mystical potion
that cures all diseases."
It's magic. so there's a decent
chance that includes Eternal Sleep.
It only takes three ingredients
to craft this Elixir of Life.
While I don't have any of them yet.
I do know exactly where they are.
But going back to that castle
as I am now is a death wish.
I need to level up more.
Stronger.
I need to get stronger.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You're saying you accept. then?
I'm saying things have changed.
Raiding a handful of C-Rank dungeons
could benefit me. so I'm in.
Yes! Yes!
That's if you agree to one condition.
Sure! Name whatever your
heart desires and it's yours!
No strike team.
Only you and I go in.
Uh...
You want the two of us to clear
19 C-Rank dungeons by ourselves?
So do we have a deal?
We can't do it. Every C-Rank raid
requires a minimum of eight hunters
to even step through the gate.
We'll take a page out
of Dongsuk Hwang's book.
Pay people to meet the quota
while we do the work.
I-I dunno.
It's a little too risky.
So think about it this way.
Fewer people going in means
less chance of casualties.
and you know
we can come out unscathed.
Clearing 19 dungeons
accident-free is huge.
And since you're doing this to persuade your
father. wouldn't a triumph like that help?
It certainly wouldn't hurt.
Boss. let's do it! Nineteen raids!
Okay. I'll handle arranging
gates and recruits!
Hmph.
Hello there. sir.
Is there something you need?
Very impressive.
I'd expect nothing less
from an S-Rank. though.
I was waiting for the right moment
to approach you. Miss Cha.
Sorry to interrupt your training.
But here. Please take my card.
It's been over a decade
since the gates first appeared.
The world has changed
at a dizzying pace.
Infrastructure. the economy.
media. and even politics.
The dungeons have affected all
of those in some shape or form.
Take our infrastructure.
It would appear the very foundation
of our lives can no longer operate
without the resources
found in the gates.
You hunters are the only ones able
to retrieve those resources. Jinho.
Then there's the Hunters Association.
The government will continue to fund them
as long as there are hunters to be overseen.
After all. without the Association.
who would assess the hunters?
How would they be
ranked and registered?
They manage gates that don't go to
auction. they handle dungeon breaks.
And yet the Association is nothing
more than a function of the state.
The ones who collect the majority
of dungeon resources
to keep our economy going
are the guilds.
Essentially. a business that's
been capitalizing on a market need.
They're are extremely wealthy because
they struck while the iron was hot.
and it's still burning.
Just look at the Hunters Guild. the
White Tiger Guild. the Reaper Guild.
the Fame Guild.
and the Knights Guild.
The five largest in the country.
They have a functional monopoly
on all dungeon-related profits.
Suits them fine. but I see no reason
we should allow that to persist.
Dungeon resources
are important to everyday life.
Simply leaving their collection to a group
of mercenaries is out of the question.
We've contributed so much
to this country. why stop now?
We should handle
this age of dungeons. too.
So. we'll establish our own guild.
You realize how crucial
that is. right. son?
I... Yes. of course.
All that may be true. but
recruiting an S-Rank hunter to act
as my brother's business
partner is such a dicey move.
Especially. when I'm right here.
Looks like none of the
extra reps count anymore.
And that Cursed Random Loot Box I was offered
for that secret quest isn't available now.
The system only let me
have one of the two.
Man. there's a chance
I could've gotten another item
as valuable
as the Demon's Castle key.
But random loot boxes aren't all bad.
I mean. the key to that instance
dungeon came from one so. maybe...
M-Maybe not.
With my stats as high
as they are now.
three points aren't enough to
make much difference anymore.
Be nice if I still had
an efficient way to level up.
Those C-Rank raids will help.
but I gotta wait on Jinho.
Oh. yeah! The penalty zone!
I can fight that centipede and...
No.
I'd have an easier time running
from that thing now. but beating it?
And what if I don't gain experience
'cause it's a punishment?
They need hunters for a D-Rank gate?
The biggest pro is that it's
a good chance to level up.
but then the con is that I'd
be fighting with a strike team.
Should I pass?
Beggars can't be choosers.
This is frustrating.
You're too good.
I didn't stand a chance.
Sure you did.
but I'm not ready to lose.
I wish you were still at your best. To
fight you in your prime would be an honor.
Come on. it's been a few months now.
When are you gonna
stop fretting over my arm?
Huh?
Another emergency summons.
Low-ranks get a lot of these for
what amounts to running errands.
But you answer.
Is retiring completely out. then?
Me. retire?
I see your point.
Not only am I getting up there in age.
I've got a missing limb to hold me back.
No! That's not what I meant. Master!
Well. I only lost my arm
when I could've lost my life.
Even though my best years are long gone.
I'd really like to spend whatever time
I have left helping people out.
My next raid request came in.
You know. honey.
Isn't it about time you considered
a career besides hunting?
-Not this again.
-It's so dangerous.
How many people died
in that one raid before?
And how close were you
to dying right along with them?
I guess pretty close.
-Daddy! Up. up!
-Eunji.
I hear you. but Eunji is starting preschool
and Eunha's going to middle school.
-so we need the money. don't we?
-I suppose. but...
It'll be fine.
The Association makes it a point not to
send lower ranks into trickier dungeons.
That one incident
was just an exception.
You're right. I'm sorry
for making such a fuss.
I get why you do. though.
Please be careful. okay?
Well. that's a given!
You know I love you.
-Hey. Daddy?
-Yeah? What's goin' on?
Are you stwong? Like superheroes?
Oh-oh. you bet I am!
Your daddy can beat up the
scariest monsters you've ever seen!
Wow! You're really.
really. really stwong. huh?
You have got some damn nerve!
Are you going to tell me why?
Don't play dumb. You wasted my
time and stuck me with that interview!
I caught it. by the way. You made
a very good impression. so bravo.
I found your answers
both insightful and sincere.
Oh. take your empty
flattery and shove it!
You should just admit that interview
was supposed to be for you. not me!
Well. let's recap the offer
made to Chairman Go.
Last I checked. they wanted a
talented hunter who had great character.
They also asked that
he be dedicated to his job.
With all that in mind. it doesn't
sound like they wanted me. does it?
Least you realize
how sketchy you are.
Ah. well.
It's done.
So. what's this about?
Though I'm glad I got to tell you off. that
can't be why you asked to speak in person.
Look behind you and you'll see
a detailed report about something
I thought should be
brought to your attention.
Yoojin Construction are getting
ready to launch their own guild.
I heard. and the moves they've
been making are pretty underhanded.
They've been headhunting at my guild.
Then I suppose since
you already know.
I have wasted your time
twice in a row now.
Yeah. well. I already know that you knew
that I knew. so can we please cut the crap?
I'll ask once more.
What's this really about?
You haven't called lately so
I'm glad I got a hold of you.
Is everything okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-Work been good?
Mm. Yeah.
You've always been such
a scaredy-cat. Joohee.
Makes it hard to picture
you bein' a hunter.
You're B-Rank. right?
I know that's supposed
to mean you're pretty strong.
but wouldn't someone with
your issues just get in the way?
Come on back home and
help run the family business.
-Your daddy's worried sick...
-Look. my life isn't yours to control!
I'm a grown woman who makes
her own choices. so just drop it!
Where in the world is all this c--
I "get in the way?"
But...
I wanna try just a bit longer.
Pardon the intrusion.
Hunter Hae-in Cha. and
what can I do for you today?
Nothing really. sir.
I just wanted to let you know a scout
from Yoojin Construction offered me a job.
Here's the card he gave me.
I see.
Apparently. they have plans
to launch a new guild soon.
and were hoping I'd join them
as their guild master. so...
They have good taste. but I assume
you're telling me this because you turned
their offer down. right?
Right. Without any hesitation. sir.
Thanks for your loyalty.
And honesty.
Of course. Also. um...
I noticed that President Baek was leaving
your office as I was on my way in. sir.
May I ask what brought him here?
I'd like to know your honest
thoughts regarding Jeju Island.
Jeju Island?
Why suddenly bring that up?
Because it should be discussed. not
sealed off and forgotten due to our failure.
But only occasional reconnaissance
is done from the shore.
and the public receives a single
annual update about any changes.
People are trying to forget it all.
To wipe the site and its
horrors from their minds.
Maybe. but you can't
exactly blame them.
Well. I refuse!
No matter how commonplace gates may
have become. or how much I get fawned over
as the "ultimate weapon" of humanity.
I will never. and I mean never.
let the memory of Jeju slip away!
I can't leave that island as it is.
which is why I intend to clear it
in the very near future.
And to accomplish that. I need you
and the others to be on the same page.
We have to grow stronger. gather allies.
and sway public opinion in our favor.
Hence the interview and
your push to train new hunters.
I would think you'd want
to return to Jeju.
Isn't there something
you left behind?
Ah. Eunseok. Byung-gu.
I'll beg you. If that's what it takes.
Just please kill them.
I'm heading out.
I can't believe you're
working on a holiday.
You sure keep busy lately.
-Yeah. I guess.
-What universe is this?
You used to have some downtime after
every gate because you would get injured.
Is all that training paying off?
Uh-huh. probably.
In any case. I have
a stable income now.
Be happy.
Uh. okay.
Hey. where's all your gear?
Hello?
Don't worry about it. See ya.
Wait. what the...?
Not like it's just a trip to
the convenience store.
Since my awakening didn't affect
my physical strength.
my sword is useless
against magical beasts.
The martial arts I've spent decades refining
don't really help my magic-based powers.
A seasoned swordsman like myself becoming
a mage hunter is quite the twist of fate.
Surely there's a reason for it.
Jinwoo?
Mister Song!
So it is you!
Wow. I hardly recognize you!
It has been a while. huh?
What are the odds
we'd just meet on the street?
I gotta say. though. what happened
to the gentle Jinwoo I used to know?
It's only been a few short months.
but you're like a new man!
Especially since I recall
you losing your right leg.
Uh. I did. but when I woke up
in the hospital. it was still there.
Well. I heard
the White Tigers found you.
Bet you anything there was a
high-ranked healer among them!
Whatever the case. you
have way too much life to live.
so it's a relief you're healed!
That's nice of you to say.
I wish you were. too.
Ah. well. maybe if I had gotten
to a decent healer in time.
but I've accepted it now.
Anyway. chance meeting or not.
I'm really glad I got to see you again.
I've been wanting to ever
since I heard you lived.
Uh. so what brought you
to this part of town?
The Association messaged me.
Said it's urgent.
I got the message too.
Hah. Now how is that
for a coincidence?
This is quite the little reunion.
You're really here.
Joohee. hey. Look at that.
The gang's all here.
Of course. they're ashamed.
We escaped with our lives. but
sacrificed Jinwoo in order to do so.
And Sang-shik also
threatened me at sword point.
No wonder he can't look me
in the eye either.
That aside. five of the six survivors
being reunited like this. makes you wonder.
Oh. my gosh. This is surreal.
You are Jinwoo. aren't you?
I am. I swear.
Your leg looks like it was
never severed and you're so tall.
I guess you were okay
the day I came to visit.
Uh. you came to visit?
We got a fine little
lady in this group. fellas.
Ditch that loser.
Why not come get hot
and heavy with me. baby!
-I know all kindsa games to play--
-Shut your dirty mouth.
This isn't a "play date."
Hunters! If you step this way.
I'll brief you on the unique
circumstances of your raid today.
Yeah. that'd be nice.
You all will be accompanied by
three prisoner substitute hunters
-who are out on good behavior.
-Substitute hunters?
You expect us
to fight alongside criminals?
It's true. they are convicted men.
However. they're here to reduce their
jail time so they shouldn't cause you grief.
We've little choice in the matter
due to the shortage of local hunters.
Please understand.
For crying out loud.
You'll also be joined by an overseer
from the Association. Taeshik Kang.
He's B-Rank. so even in
the worst-case scenario.
he'll be able to handle
three C-Rank criminals with ease.
So. you can rest assured.
Something isn't right.
Hey. maybe you should
sit this out. Joohee?
Are you bailing. too?
No. I'm going.
All right. then so am I.
Fair enough.
Damn. it's good to be free.
even if we gotta work for it.
Chainin' us like animals.
You're the good guys. so why so evil?
Shut up.
You're chained
'cause you're convicts.
And you know what happens if
you act up while the chains are off.
As my associate previously mentioned.
I'm Taeshik Kang of the Surveillance Team.
I'll be keeping an eye on those three
throughout the raid. so you can relax.
We'll need a leader. though.
Do we have any volunteers?
What do you say? Think you'd
be willing to follow my lead again?
Of course. I would. sir.
I appreciate you giving
me this chance.
Uh. you don't have to bow.
On that day. seven
people died because of me.
The magnitude of my failure
cannot be understated.
But six of us did make
it out. because of you.
So let me say this
on behalf of all the survivors.
I am so grateful to you.
Mister Song. Stand up. please.
Hmm.
And what about you. Sangshik?
Do you care if I take the lead?
If that's what you want. go ahead.
Right.
Well. it's settled.
I volunteer to take point
in today's raid.
Thank you for your courage.
Let's get underway then.
Brace yourselves. everyone.
Here we go.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm